soon I'm gonna do like a special like I'm gonna do a small doses episode that's my podcast on
side effects of depression it's gonna really just be about like my personal experiences with
depression because depression shows up different for everybody but for me it's like a trap door in
a fun house so like you go in the fun house knowing that there could be trap doors what I
mean by that is that like I'd be knowing like oh it's coming I can feel the depression coming and
I'd be trying to do all type of shit like try and fight it off and then it'll just
trap door and I'm in it and then like you know I just kind of got to like wade my way through
and out of it but um and sometimes you know there's like a myriad of things that will like just kind of
end it and sometimes it'll just be like oh no I'm out of it or sometimes it might be a situation like
today I had lunch with Randy Jackson who is like the best it's a yes for me dog and I feel like that
kind of helped me out of it but yeah that episode's coming because emoji